[school bell ringing]
All right class, settle down—and
Takanashi, will you stop looking out
the window again as if you're some main
character?
That means you too, Pikachu.
Pikachu!
[music]
I possess the Eye of the Wicked Lord!
Rikka Takanashi!
Reality rejected, be banished
from this world!
Yeah, you get the gist.
Operation: "Get Senpai to Notice Me"
starts now!
[PHIA]: Do you want to know about
the Ugandan Knuckles?
[AYAME]: Then you pretend you like
his interests!
And boom! Love at first sight.
You've come to the right place!
[RIKKA]: There's one little bitty issue.
It's through the forbidden portals.
Okay, we tried.
After excruciating hours of research,
I've concluded
you have ventured through the forbidden
portals and returned safely.
Is that correct?
Oh, I see what this is.
Luffy! Was this your doing?
The good old orphan joke, huh?
That's why you're gonna be the
King of Pirates one day.
Keep it up.
- [RIKKA]: Hey!
I'm not an orphan or a joke.
Alright, then where are your parents?
Um... Overseas business trip?
That happens a lot around here.
What a bunch of irresponsible parents.
Okay, look. I'll give you this.
[dramatic music]
[RIKKA]: Um, what's it like?
Kid, you have no idea.
[ROSHI]: You planning on coming back
this time?
Know your place, Takanashi. You will
never, ever be good enough for Deku.
[RIKKA]: So, what exactly is the plan here
Take portals to different worlds until
we find a Knuckles?
Yeah, something like that.
What's the PC Quest?
- I don't know.
[RIKKA]: It helped a bit, you know...
to pretend I was someone else.
At least for a little while.
[KAKASHI]: This universe has
no boundaries.
Be whatever you want to be.
You don't need to pretend.
Just don't go flying around
or you'll get us both banned.
[music]
[Titan roars]
[metal clanging]
Wow, such a pretty mirror.
- Wow, what a pretty mirror...
Heheheh... Don't cry, it's only your leg.
- [POOH]: First time?
- [KAKASHI]: Uh... Yeah...
- [RIKKA]: He's just hungry.
- [KAKASHI] Uh... Yeah...
- [RIKKA]: Good Knuckles. So ungrateful,
Midoriya.
- [POOH]: Mirror dwelling can get
- [RIKKA]: Good Knuckles. So ungrateful,
Midoriya.
- [POOH]: the best of us.